

NAME

Frontend Developer

Aaron Fabricio Santa Cruz Valdez

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a self-taught person with 3 years of experience in web development. I create, design, update, maintain websites I have extensive knowledge of client-side development (Frontend), I have basic knowledge of the (Backend) with different technologies. I live in La Paz, Bolivia. Am in constant training learning new web technologies.

CONTACTS

La Paz - Bolivia



aaronfabricio00@gmail.com



+59170668135



https://www.linkedin.com/in/aar on-fabricio-santa-cruz-valdez/



https://aaroncode.net/

EDUCATION

- University Boliviana de Informática
- Platzi(Programming)

ABILITIES

- Web programming.
- Frontend Developer
- SEO
- Website audit
- Desktop and mobile web design
- Basic computer hardware technician.
- Basic cell phone technician

TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT. TYPESCRIPT
- SASS, LESS, STYLUS.
- MONGODB, MYSQL
- BOOTSTRAP, MATERIALIZE, TAILWINDCSS.
- NPM AND DEPENDENCES
- WEBPACK
- GIT. GITHUB
- REACT JS, ANGULAR
- PHP WITH LARAVEL
- WORDPRESS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Datec

MAY 2022 - JUL 2022

 Consultant and collaborator in the update of the proflexUI4 software design for ATMs+

Goosistem

SEP 2021 - OCT 2021

 Development of the website https://goosistem.com/ with HTML CSS and JAVASCRIPT

LANGUAGES

- Spanish (Advanced)
- English(Reading and writing)



NOMBRE

Frontend Developer

Aaron Fabricio Santa Cruz Valdez

PERFIL PERSONAL

Soy una persona autodidacta con 3 años de experiencia en desarrollo web. Creo, diseño, actualizo, mantengo sitios web Tengo un amplio conocimiento del desarrollo del lado del cliente (Frontend), tengo conocimientos básicos del (Backend) con diferentes tecnologías. Vivo en La Paz, Bolivia. Estoy en constante formación aprendiendo nuevas tecnologías web.

CONTACTOS



_

aaronfabricio00@gmail.com

+59170668135

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aar on-fabricio-santa-cruz-valdez/

https://aaroncode.net/

EDUCACIÓN

- Universidad Boliviana de Informática
- Platzi(Programación)

HABILIDADES

- Programación web.
- Desarrollador Frontend
- SEO
- Auditoria a sitios web
- Diseño web desktop y movil
- Técnico básico hardware Computadores.
- Técnico básico en celulares

TECNOLOGÍAS

- HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT
- SASS, LESS, STYLUS.
- MONGODB, MYSQL
- BOOTSTRAP, MATERIALIZE, TAILWINDCSS.
- NPM Y DEPENDENCIAS
- WEBPACK
- GIT. GITHUB
- REACT JS, ANGULAR
- PHP CON LARAVEL
- WORDPRESS

EXPERIENCIA DE TRABAJO

Datec

MAY 2022 - JUL 2022

 Consultor y colaborador en la actualización del diseño de proflexUI4 software para ATMs

Goosistem

SEP 2021 - OCT 2021

 Desarrollo del sitio web https://goosistem.com/ con HTML CSS y JAVASCRIPT

IDIOMAS

- Español (Avanzado)
- Ingles (Lectura y escritura)